{
    "subject": "Lucien_Hubbard",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Rose-Marie__1928_film_",
    "human_readable": "Lucien Hubbard created the film Rose-Marie (1928).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.841589093208313,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Lucien Hubbard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7567412257194519,
            "question": "Who directed the film Rose-Marie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7298055291175842,
            "question": "In what year was the film Rose-Marie released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6549544334411621,
            "question": "Was Rose-Marie a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5977986454963684,
            "question": "Is Lucien Hubbard known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5179426670074463,
            "question": "Who were some of the actors in Rose-Marie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5012280941009521,
            "question": "What genre is the film Rose-Marie likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.500903308391571,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Rose-Marie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4141245186328888,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Lucien Hubbard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36628827452659607,
            "question": "What other films were popular in 1928?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lucien Hubbard created the film Rose-Marie (1928).",
            "html": "yago_11381_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other films directed by Lucien Hubbard?",
            "html": "yago_11381_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Rose-Marie?",
            "html": "yago_11381_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Rose-Marie likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_11381_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11381_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Lucien Hubbard created the film Rose-Marie (1928).\" Specifically, file_path `75.txt` states that \"Rose-Marie is a 1928 American drama film directed by Lucien Hubbard,\" and `34.txt` mentions his role as the director of the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}